The Guitar is a romance, drama, music film directed by Amy Redford.
The life of a woman is transformed after she is diagnosed with a terminal
disease, fired from her job and abandoned by her boyfriend.
Given two months to live, she throws caution to the wind to pursue her dreams.
Melody, played by Saffron Burrows.
Roscoe Wasz, played by Isaach de Bankolé.
Cookie, played by Paz de la Huerta.
Mr. Laffs, played by Adam Trese.
Dr. Murray, played by Janeane Garofalo.
Brett, played by Reg Rogers.
The Guitar is a 2008 American drama film directed
and co-produced by Amy Redford.
It stars Saffron Burrows as a woman who decides to pursue her dreams after being diagnosed
with a terminal disease, fired from her job and abandoned by her boyfriend.
The film explores themes of new york city, guitar,
shower, penthouse apartment, cubicle.
The tone is emotional.